export const questions = [
  {
    id: 1,
    type: "input.number",
    question: "How many questions do you have to answer correctly at least to save the world?",
    correct: 6,
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    type: "input.text",
    question: "What is the AKA of the leader of the machines? Be careful...is case sensitive!",
    correct: "LOM",
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    type: "select",
    question: "What material was Pinocchio made of?",
    options: { a: "Gum", b: "Iron", c: "Rock", d: "Wood" },
    correct: "d",
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    type: "colors",
    question: "The Japanese flag has a large dot in the center. Can you tell what its color is? Read carefully...",
    options: { a: "blue", b: "yellow", c: "red" },
    correct: "c",
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    type: "input.number",
    question: "Solve the following operation:<br/><br/>5 - 3 * 2 + 4 / 2",
    correct: 1,
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    type: "select",
    question: "What question number are you answering right now?",
    options: { a: 1, b: 2, c: 3, d: 4, e: 5, f: 6, g: 7, h: 8, i: 9, j: 10 },
    correct: "index",
    trick: "index",
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    type: "checkbox",
    question: "X-X+X+X-X",
    options: { a: "Z", b: "Y", c: "X" },
    correct: "c",
    trick: "blink",
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    type: "checkbox",
    question: "What was the first cryptocurrency to come out, which is established as a reserve of value?",
    options: { a: "DOGE COIN", b: "BITCOIN", c: "ETHEREUM" },
    correct: "b",
    trick: "lom",
    seconds: 15,
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    type: "checkbox",
    question: "I hope you have been paying attention all this time in LOM because I want you to tell me what color his eyes are...",
    options: { a: "brown", b: "purple", c: "red" },
    correct: "c",
    trick: "blink.colors.grayscale",
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    type: "input.text",
    question: "CoUnTxXxXxOnEuPpErOnElOwEr",
    correct: "FiVe",
    trick: "blink.lom.blur",
  },
]